{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910118647","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910118647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910119610","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910119610"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kusoma kusoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910122531","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910122531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNATAKA"," userResponse":" KUNATAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910123064","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910123064"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MACHO"," userResponse":" MACHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910123707","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910123707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunataka macho yaone"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAONE"," userResponse":" YAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910127802","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910127802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASIKIO"," userResponse":" MASIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910128725","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910128724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910128984","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910128984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910129050","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910129050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" d22a9034-2148-486a-9ef5-fd804d423d34"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Kusoma_Welcome_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Masikio yasikie"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIKIE"," userResponse":" YASIKIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910147371","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910147370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" 19f923b3-40eb-4ddd-9394-a311116c0266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910155946","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910155945"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" 19f923b3-40eb-4ddd-9394-a311116c0266"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.noShow.25"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_U-E-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PLACEMENT"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910166810","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910166810"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" 3c934ef6-5098-4c38-b98d-69d7f0078f39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910167244","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910167244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" 3c934ef6-5098-4c38-b98d-69d7f0078f39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910167728","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910167728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" 3c934ef6-5098-4c38-b98d-69d7f0078f39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910168373","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910168373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" 3c934ef6-5098-4c38-b98d-69d7f0078f39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1547910168471","data":{"timestamp":" 1547910168471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190119_180143"," gameId":" 3c934ef6-5098-4c38-b98d-69d7f0078f39"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}